easy2.com 2015-06-14

# Easy2 Technologies - interactive merchandising solutions that connect manufacturers, retailers, and shoppers.

##### Easy2 Website Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by Easy2® Technologies, Inc. (together with its affiliates, "Easy2," "we" or "us."). Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us and we want to make your online experience satisfying and safe. By using or accessing this website, you signify your acknowledgment and agreement to this Privacy Policy. Do not use this website if you do not agree to this policy. “Affiliate” means an entity which controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with Easy2® Technologies, Inc., and “control” means direct or indirect ownership or control of 50% or more of the voting rights of Easy2Technologies, Inc. or such entity.

This privacy statement discloses what information we gather about our users and how we use it.

##### INFORMATION EASY2 GATHERS AND TRACKS

Easy2 gathers two types of information about users:

1) Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. Information requested may include personally identifiable information (“PII”) such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number, as well as demographic information. This data is aggregated and analyzed so we can learn more about our customers, their purchasing behavior and habits, and product needs.

2) Information Easy2 gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience.

##### Under no circumstances does Easy2 divulge any PII about an individual user to a third party. 

Our website also allows you to contact us directly with questions or comments regarding our products. This process requires you to give us certain PII, including your e-mail address, so that you may answer your questions.  All opinions, ideas, suggestions, and other feedback submitted via email or our website may be used by Easy2 without any restriction and free of charge. 

Easy2 Gathers PII in the following processes: 

##### Optional Voluntary Information 

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of PII by users:

**1) Electronic newsletters**

We may offer our site users a free electronic newsletter. Easy2 gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. 

**2)"Share This" Service**

We may offer our site users the ability to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "ShareThis". The user must provide the user’s email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

**3) Polling**

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Easy2 may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with PII about individual users. 

**4) Surveys**

Easy2 may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party. 

_**Children**_

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request PII from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

**Cookies**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself may contain PII and will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Easy2 uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in polling and surveys. 

##### SECURITY

Easy2 has taken precautions to prevent unauthorized access to the site and data collected therein but no server is completely secure, and we cannot be responsible for loss, corruption or unauthorized acquisition of PII gained through the site. 

Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

##### LINKS TO OTHER SITES 

This site contains links to third-party retailers, business partners and sites. Because such linked sites are not under our control, we are not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any information or content contained on these sites. Use of these sites is at your own risk, and if you choose to provide any PII directly to any of these sites, the privacy policy of that site will govern use of your provided PII. We make no guarantees, explicit or implied, regarding any linked sites. 

##### OPT-IN / OPT-OUT POLICY

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters. We ask customers that wish to receive communications from us to "Opt-in" when they register their product warranty or ask to be placed on our email list. 

*Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas. 

##### YOUR CONSENT 

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Easy2. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.   Once any changes that we make to this privacy policy become effective, your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of the new terms.
